Mișcă sau te calc în picioare!
Nu! Nu te apropia!
Oameni care mănâncă alți oameni?
Nu e nimic amuzant în asta.
Asta nu e adevărat.
E imposibil să fie adevărat.
Nu-i așa, mami?
Am dreptate, nu?
Unde te duci, Takagi?
Ce? Aveai altceva de făcut?
Păi, mă gândeam să merg în cancelarie...
Asta e stupid.
Ce crezi că ar putea face profesorii noștri?
Dar, Takagi...
În această...
În această situație...
Am o întrebare.
C-Ce anume?
Vrei să mori? Sau vrei să trăiești?
Păi, ei bine...
Privește. Sunt câteva persoane la ușa cancelariei care au avut aceeași idee ca si tine.
Domnilor profesori!
Eu vreau să trăiesc!
Ai înțeles?
Așa că mișcă-ți fundul!
Am înțeles!
Haide...
Takashi, te implor...
Vreau să mor fiind eu însumi.
Nu se va...
Nu se va transforma în unul din ei!
Oprește-te!
Ce este?
Ei bine, vreau să știu ce naiba se petrece.
Asta a fost destul de direct.
De ce aș minți?
Îmi poți împrumuta puțin telefonul? Vreau să încerc să-l sun pe tata.
Știu că este polițist, dar cum îl vei contacta
când linia de urgența a poliției e ocupată?
Mi-a lăsat un număr privat pe care nu ar trebui să-l folosesc în mod normal.
Sună!
Tată?
Alo?
Acest număr de telefonul...
este al lui Takashi?
Tată?
Tată, ascultă. Suntem la
școală în acest moment...
Alo? Takashi?
Call Duration
Probabil ai acest număr de la Rei.
Ea este bine?
Semnalul meu...
Tată?! Nu mă poți auzi?!
Ascultă, întregul oraș este
într-o stare de panică.
Tată? Tată!
Bine?
Întregul oraș este
într-o stare de panică!
Trebuie să vă evacuați...
Out of Range
End of Call
Fără semnal?
Dar tocmai ce sunase!
De ce? De ce?!
Rei!
Takashi...
Tata...
Nici măcar nu m-a recunoscut...
T-Takagi, ai cumva telefonul la tine? Știu că e împotriva regulilor, dar...
Sunt o elevă de onoare!
Chiar dacă l-aș avea, pe cine aș suna?
Păi, ei bine, la poliție...
Tu chiar ești prost.
Privește cât de gravă e situația.
Nu crezi că a încercat
cineva deja să sune la poliție?
Nu am auzit nicio sirenă până acum, nu?
Înțelegi acum?
Întregul oraș e cuprins de haos?
Probabil.
Poliția a fost trimisă deja, probabil.
Dar uită-te la acest loc...
Ar trebui să sunăm la...
Forțele Armate?
Nu m-aș baza nici pe ei.
Știu că nu pot fi trimiși pentru apărare sau securitate publică, fără ordine de la guvern, dar...
Nu mă refer la asta!
Atunci, ce încerci să...
Sunt în aceeași situație precum poliția.
Haide să presupunem că oameni din toată Japonia se mănâncă reciproc. Ce crezi că se întâmplă?
Ascultă, sunt 130 de milioane
de oameni în Japonia.
Din cei 130 de milioane, câți crezi
că fac parte din Forțele Armate?
Furthermore, who's to say
that this hasn't affected the SDF?
Haide să ieșim de aici.
B-Bine!
Sigh. I'm stuck with fatass here since Komuro ran off.
What a drag.
Nurse's Office
O-Okada...
Okada?
Crap!
Sorry! Sorry!
Whatever shall I do?
Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
Sorry! Sorry!
Sorry!
I'm sorry!
I can't get a hold of the police or the fire department.
I could treat people, but they're screwed once they get bitten,
and they come back to life after they die.
I feel like I'm in one of those movies that weirdos like.
Is it really that amazing?
Let's go, Shizuka-sensei!
Hold on a sec.
I should take whatever I can carry.
Please hurry!
Shizuka-sensei!
Run away! Quickly!
Uh... What'd you say your name was again?
Huh?
H-Hey now...
I am Busujima Saeko, captain of the Kendo Club.
Tell me, 2nd year, what is your name?
Ishii... Kazu...
Ishii-kun, you fought bravely to protect Dr. Marikawa.
Your courage is nothing short of praiseworthy.
Do you know what happens to
you once you have been bitten?
Do you want your parents or friends to see you like that?
If you do not,
then I shall end your life for you here and now.
Though, I've never killed anyone before.
P-Please...
W-Wait a sec, what—
You're the school nurse, I got it, but stay out of it.
One of our duties as women is to protect a man's pride.
What do we do now that we're here, Takagi-san?
Some of it does look useful, but—
Shut up, you fat nerd.
Lock the door so they don't come in here!
I-It's locked!
Are we going to use these as weapons?
You're one of those so-called military nerds or gun freaks, aren't you?
Haven't you seen an action movie with one of these?
A nail gun?
It's gas powered?
Well duh!
You wouldn't be able to carry it around if it
had a compressor like in the movies, would you?
Jeez, so stupid.
Do you like movies?
Don't be so stupid!
I'm an all-knowing genius!
We have an extra gas canister and extra nails here. Nothing to worry about.
How could you not be worried?
They're coming!
They're coming from the hallway!
I'd say it weighs 9 pounds.
On par with an older assault rifle.
But my stance will be messed up. It needs a sight.
Hey, are you ignoring me?!
Hirano?
No!
Gotcha!
Hirano?
Ready?
Ready!
Turn it on!
Crap.
Could you put the drill and nails over there in a bag?
Excuse me?!
Who gave you the right to order me around?!
Pretty please?
Okay.
Takashi!
It's okay.
They sound happy to see us.
You' all feel great, don't you?
Take this!
What do you think you're doing? You should carry something too.
H-Hey, Takagi-san...
Mind if I ask you something?
What?
Uhh, why me?
No reason in particular.
Oh, okay...
What's with the sudden mood swing?
Did you come to a realization?
I don't know, I guess I did!
Hirano!
Yes!
Gotta hand it to you. It was a good idea to use the fire hose.
Well, the water pressure is so strong.
Don't you remember when we were in middle
school and we had that fire drill and you and Hisashi...
I'll be sure to remember it this time.
I think I'm ready to go now.
It'll be rough in there. You sure?
Let's go.
Where are we going?
Home.
We'll head to our houses and help survivors along the way.
This is our hometown. We should be able to feel our way around.
Yeah... Yeah!
I know my dad is safe, so...
Hey, you should call your house soon.
I will sooner or later.
My dad lives away from home because of his job,
and my mom is an elementary school teacher, so she wouldn't be at home either.
They probably wouldn't shut up if I got a hold of them anyway.
Jeez, we shouldn't be laughing right now.
I wasn't being serious about that, of course.
When I looked at how things were at my own school,
it frightened me to think of what it was like at my mom's school.
Wh-What are you doing?
Shut up and watch.
Do you understand now?
See how he didn't react when that rag hit him?
They don't feel pain, so they only react to sound.
I don't think they can see or he
wouldn't have bumped into that locker.
What about, say, heat?
We'll try it if we have to.
Let's move.
Are we really gonna go outside?
What's wrong with that?
Uhm, I don't like walking...
This is why I hate fat nerds!
I don't wanna hear you complain about
walking until you're old enough to drive!
The staff room? What a difficult request you have made.
But everyone keeps their car keys in there...
Hey, why don't you just kill them?
It should be easy for you...
Stopping to crush the head of everything we come across
would accomplish nothing other than to slow us down.
We would become surrounded.
It would be hard for us to get
away should one of them take hold.
Wow, you really thought about this.
Oh jeez! What was that?
Such fashion is unsuitable for running.
This is a brand name skirt!
Are your clothes or your life more important?
...both!
What's that sound?
Was that from the staff room?
I won't be able to figure out more of their traits if you keep killing them!
Help me fight them, Takagi-san!
Why the hell do I have to fight?!
I'm almost out of ammo!
So?! Why don't you just reload it?
But... behind you...
Hirano!
I'm out!
Don't you dare come near me!
Takagi-san!
Go away...
Go away!
I'm sick of these things! I want my mom!
I will take the right!
Rei!
And I got the left!
Takagi-san...
Takagi-san, are you okay?
Miyamoto...
We are all acquainted with the school nurse, yes?
I am Busujima Saeko from 3-A.
I'm Komuro Takashi from 2-B.
You're the same Busujima-senpai who
won at the national championship last year?
I'm in the Sojutsu Club. My name is Miyamoto Rei.
I'm, uhm, Hirano Kouta from B.
Nice to meet all of you.
What the... You're all so soft.
"Senpai"? Seriously?
You two got held back a year,
so you guys are the same age.
Hey now, Takagi...
Don't treat me like I'm stupid!
I'm a genius!
I can do anything once I put my mind to it!
I'm... I'm...
Enough.
That is quite enough.
Look at how dirty I am...
I need to tell Mama to get it cleaned...
My inhuman cheek, wet with red,
aka ni nureru hoo no mukishitsu ga
drives me nuts
kanjou wo kuruwaseru
So stay by my side forever, always watching over me
dakara zutto boku no soba ni itte zutto mimamotteite
Now I forget it all as my body
fukai yami ni karada wo atsumete
gets taken by the vile darkness
ima wa subete wo wasure yo
Your fiery voice fights the darkness and heals my heart
hageshii koe ga kokoro wo iyashite yami wo tatsukara
Your face is like that of an angel
hikari no naka dakarete nemuru
sleeping snugly in the light
tenshi no youna yokogao ni
Those of us who came to know sadness
kodoku wo shitta bokutachi wa tada
just wonder if we can lean on it alone
sugaritakatta dake nano kana
Think it'll hold?
I believe we are all exhausted.
Let us rest here for a short while.
Takagi-san, are you okay?
G-Glasses?
What about them?
My contacts kept falling out!
Glasses...
Here, Takashi.
Oh, thank you.
Where are your car keys, Marikawa-sensei?
Oh, they're in my bag.
Say, is your vehicle spacious enough to seat all of us?
Now that you mention it...
What of the miniature buses used for club
activities? The keys hang from the wall in here.
They're here!
That should work, but where are we going?
To check on our families.
We'll stop by everyone's home going from closest to furthest.
And if we have to, we'll help our families too.
Once we're done, we'll find a safe place to stay.
What is it?
What the...
What's up, Rei?
...government has begun to consider emergency measures
against the outbreaks that have been occuring all over the place.
However, all the political parties have been expressing their uncertainty about the SDF's security operations.
Revolt? They're calling this a revolt?
Emergency News Coverage
The number of deaths in the Saitama prefecture already exceeds 10,000.
The prefecture governor has—
That was gunfire!
Just now, the police opened fire!
But what are they shooting at?!
No! What?! Stay away!
Help me!
Emergency News Coverage